- johnmichael076589@gmail.c
 om
- ★ 2106 Norwalk Ave Los Angeles, CA 90041
- 🛗 Date of birth 04/20/1991
- % https://emptyfist.github.io
- □ Japanese
- Reloate
 Commute
 Remote
- 231 276 1888
- Married (with child)

Skills

Problem Solver

Fast Learner

Languages

Chinese

English

Japanese

Interests

Sport&eSport

Social networks

- **S** @live:.cid.d4cbb78a01318aa8
- in @john-michael-671793254
- @emptyfist

John Michael

Senior Front End Engineer

My career goal is to move into management as a CTO, and I know this role would help me hone my leadership skills.

About me

Highly capable, versatile and accomplished Senior IT Engineer with more than 8 years extensive management experience, planning and implementing. I have indepth knowledge of Information Technology, Finance domain, Decentralized Finance and NFT Marketplaces and participated in Web-software development as Full Stack Engineer.

The important is that I'm always carefully analyzing the specifications, we always try to understand what the customer wants, what we want to achieve using the system, and the risks after the release, so that we can provide a system that is easy for users to use. In addition, when participating in a project, regardless of "employment form", look at the project from a bird's-eye view and fulfill your position and role, while at the same time following up the work and mentality of all team members.

Education

Bachelor's Degree

From September 2008 to April 2012
Information Science, Tokyo University Tokyo, Japan

Department of Information Science, Faculty of Science

Work experience

Web3 Front End Engineer

Since January 2022 Faculty Group Panama

- Built Pixel-based modern style Front End
- Integrated third-party API such as EMailJS and Web3 in FE
- Used WS/WSS and Fetch APIS to communicate with BE
- Provided high quality and speed of FE creation as intended by the design team
- Customized all components and integrated smooth transition and animations
- Deployment

https://faculty.group/, https://facultyentertainment.com, https://otaris.io, https://www.spool.fi

Full Stack Developer

From January 2021 to December 2021 LeadEdge Consulting Co., LTD Tokyo, Japan

- Developed NFT Market place able to integrate with opensea.io
- Collection based Mint System(Lazy Mint for Zero gas fee) base on ERC721
- IPFS storage for content upload and implemented Firebase
- Built out a new version of front-end application using NextJS
- Implemented event monitoring on Web3.js
- Multi-chain integration (Ethereum, Polygon)
- Introduced Staking, Liquidity Pool, NFT market place
- Built CI/CD Pipelines on GitHub for Test and Deploy
- Deployment: https://leadedge-c.com/

Assets

Vehicle

Work experience

Full Stack Developer

From September 2021 to March 2022 ASUENE Co,.LTD Shinagawa, Japan

- Arranged Front-End UI elements with Vuetify and customized theme upon it.
- Integrated third-party APIS using Laravel
- Managed GCP, GCS and auto-run batch using Laravel
- Database design
- Analyzed and displayed statistics data using D3
- Role as DevOps to build docker environment, implement Nginx, Redis, make CI/CD pipelines on GitHub for Test and Deploy
- Deployment: https://earthene.com

C# Developer

From April 2012 to August 2015 SilverStar Japan Co.,LTD Gifu, Japan

- Role as Disassembly engineer to decompile previous versioned file
- Arrange UI with Ribbon UI component, file version manage, Undo/Redo manage with AIR&C#
- Design Database and make Restful API for Front-End
- Made Undo/Redo data structure and algorithms
- Implemented Scanner and Printer mechanism, SpreadSheet into C# component
- Programmed detail test cases using C# Unit

Computer skills

Front End

- React.js, Redux, Next.js
- · Vue.js, VueX
- HTML&CSS
- SASS&TailwndCSS&Bootstrap
- JS&TS&jQuery

BlockChain

- Web3.js, Ethers.js
- Smart Contract
- TheGraph

DevOps

- CI/CD, PipeLine
- · AWS, Docker

Back End

- Node.js(Express)
- PHP(Laravel)
- MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB
- Java